Guide to the Kilpatrick Collection of Cherokee Manuscripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Notebook #15
  - Church notes, 1946 May 12 (Box 14, Folder 1249)
  - Birth or death records, after 1944 (Box 14, Folder 1250)
  - Unidentified note on envelope, undated (Box 14, Folder 1251)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Unidentified Collection II, obtained from Siquanid' Dil'tideg [Sikwanida Diltidegi Baby Pig Jumper] Summer 1962"
  - Financial document with Eastern Emigrant and Western Cherokee notarized seal, 1926 August 27 (Box 14, Folder 1252)
  - Short hymn, undated (Box 14, Folder 1253)
  - Letter to the author's brother, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 1254)
  - Letter to Mulberry Tree Church, 1926 December 6 (Box 14, Folder 1255)
  - Nvya, Diganiyiski (Rock, Catcher). Journal or notebook, circa 1949 (Box 14, Folder 1256)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Diganiyiski Nvya V"
  - Suli, Tsugonadv. Letter, "Commandment for an old Cherokee Indian", 1931 August 25 (Box 14, Folder 1257)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Tsugonadv Suli Coll. (2 pieces)"
  - Chant, undated (Box 14, Folder 1258)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Tsatsi Wili Secular Coll."
  - Chant, undated (Box 14, Folder 1259)
  - Political document or address, 1901 October 3 (Box 14, Folder 1260)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 53-54
  - Account or myth about visiting a shaman, undated (Box 14, Folder 1261)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 95-96
  - Personal letter or journal, 1946 March 2 (Box 14, Folder 1262)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 97-98
  - Account of a meeting regarding a community garden, 1941 August 20 (Box 14, Folder 1263)
  - Unidentified note or short text, undated (Box 14, Folder 1264)
  - Cherokee and English names, undated (Box 14, Folder 1265)
  - Notice or memo, title "itsitsalagi itsehvi (you Cherokee where you live)", undated (Box 14, Folder 1266)
  - Notes on spells and shamanism, undated (Box 14, Folder 1267)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 88-89
  - Envelope with name on verso, "Tsatsi Wili (George Williams)", after 1941 July 22 (Box 14, Folder 1268)
  - List of names and death dates, circa 1941 (Box 14, Folder 1269)
  - Commentary on verses of the Bible, undated (Box 14, Folder 1270)
  - Letter, signed "A.W.H.", 1952 December 18 (Box 14, Folder 1271)
  - Letter, 1953 January 26 (Box 14, Folder 1272)
  - George, Charlotte. Letter, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 1273)
  - Hummingbird, Gus. Letter to Davis Standingdeer, 1925 October 17 (Box 15, Folder 1274)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Gus Hummingbird Doc."
  - Historical note or list with years, undated (Box 15, Folder 1275)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Andy Grasshopper Doc."
  - Handle, Ed. Account of missionary work, organization, and funding, 1931 August 11 (Box 15, Folder 1276)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Adelagadiya Doc."
  - Stayathome, John. Hymns, undated (Box 15, Folder 1277)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "John Stayathome Doc."
  - Letter to Diganiyisgi Nvya (Catcher Rock) relating to church matters, undated (Box 15, Folder 1278)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Diganiyisgi Nvya Secular coll."
  - Financial record, 1919 June 25 (Box 15, Folder 1279)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 70-71
  - Address (in English) with short Cherokee note, undated (Box 15, Folder 1280)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 15, Folder 1281)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 15, Folder 1282)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 15, Folder 1283)
  - Receipt, 1946 July 3 (Box 15, Folder 1284)
  - Financial record, undated (Box 15, Folder 1285)
  - Snake Cree district financial record, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 1286)
  - Hymns written on envelope, undated (Box 15, Folder 1287)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "George Washington Doc. (used to teach his son to write tsalagi)"
  - Medical formula (photocopies) and Envelope "Joseph E. Foreman Collection 6", after 1962 June 9 (Box 15, Folder 1288)
  - Fourkiller, Charles. Church records describing Sunday activities, 1932 October 12 (Box 15, Folder 1289)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Fairfield Church Records Collection (obtained 1962)"
  - Church committee notes, 1915 April 26 (Box 15, Folder 1290)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 66-67
  - Church service, 1927 March 27 (Box 15, Folder 1291)
  - Church service, 1923 January 21 (Box 15, Folder 1292)
  - Church records, voting for leaders, undated (Box 15, Folder 1293)
  - Sunday school attendance, undated (Box 15, Folder 1294)
- Notebook #12: "Medicine Books"
  - Kilpatrick notebook cover, "12 Medicine Books", undated (Box 15, Folder 1295)
  - Christian Songbook, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 1296)
    Note inside cover in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Copied by Joe Coon (June, 1962) who had the translations made"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1297)
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1298)
    Found with note in pencil Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Dlanusi Doyanisi VII"; with additonal note in pen in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "1940s?"
  - Diganiyisgi Nvya. Journal or Diary, circa 1950 (Box 15, Folder 1299)
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1300)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Dlanusi Doyanisi VI"
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1301)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Green Waterdown[?] 1939-1940"
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1302)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Unidentified I"
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1303)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Green Waterdown II"; additional note in ink, "1940-41"
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "diganiyisgi uya IV"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1304)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Dludlu Ugisi[?]di II"; additional note in ink, "also text to horse dance 1943"
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1940 (Box 15, Folder 1305)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "dlanusi doyanisi V"
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1942 (Box 15, Folder 1306)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Dan Scott trans. 1942-1943"
  - Medical formula notebook, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 1307)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Dan Wilson Book 1954"
  - Sam, Levi. Medical formula notebook, circa 1943 (Box 15, Folder 1308)
    Note on first page in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Duncan Book I Dec. 1964"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1309)
    Note on first page in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Duncan Book 4 Dec. 1964"
  - Medical formula and syllabary practice notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1310)
    In envelope with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Egi [sorin crossed out] Formula Book I (42) circa 1940"
  - Medical formula noteboook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1311)
    Inside envelope with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf 1944? Dlanus' Toyanis Formula Book X 1944"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1312)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf I"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1313)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf V"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1314)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf VI"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1315)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, " Arch Wolf sec. Book II"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1316)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Diganiyisgi Nvya [Catcher Rock] III 1947"
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1317)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf II 1951"
  - Wolf, Arch. Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 15, Folder 1318)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Arch Wolf Sec. Book IV"
  - Medical formula notebook and Envelope labeled, "Siquanid' Diltidesi Formula Book IV", circa 1962 (Box 16, Folder 1319)
  - Journal and medical formula notebook, circa 1944 (Box 16, Folder 1320)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "1944"
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 16, Folder 1321)
    Note on front cover of notebook, "Oklahoma - Formulas Hummingbird Collection, Transcribed by Rev William Jumper (1962)"
  - Jumper, Charlie. Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1322)
    Note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand on first page, "Siquanida V"
  - Notebook with medical formula, church documents, hymns, 1963 July 1 (Box 16, Folder 1323)
    Note on first page in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Siquanida VI"
- Notebook #3: "Uwedasat Collection XXXI XXXIII"
  - Kilpatrick notebook cover #3, "Uwedasat Collection XXXI XXXIII", undated (Box 16, Folder 1324)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1325)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Uwedasat' Collection XXXI (on larger sheets)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1326)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1327)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1328)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1329)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1330)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1331)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1332)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1333)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1334)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1335)
  - Hymns, undated (Box 16, Folder 1336)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1337)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1338)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1339)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1340)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1341)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1342)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1343)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1344)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1345)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1346)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1347)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1348)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1349)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1350)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1351)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1352)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1352)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1353)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1354)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1355)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1356)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1357)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1358)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1359)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1360)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1361)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1362)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1363)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1364)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1365)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1366)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1367)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1368)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1369)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1370)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1371)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1372)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1373)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1374)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1375)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1376)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1377)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1378)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1379)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1380)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1381)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1382)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1383)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1384)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1385)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1386)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1387)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1388)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1389)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 16, Folder 1390)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1391)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1392)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1393)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1394)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1395)
  - Unidentified note fragment, undated (Box 17, Folder 1396)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1397)
  - Syllabary chart and short text, undated (Box 17, Folder 1398)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1399)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1400)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1401)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1402)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1403)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1404)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1405)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1406)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1407)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1408)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1409)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1410)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Uwedasat' Collection XXXIII (fragments)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1411)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1412)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1413)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1414)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1415)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1416)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1417)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1418)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1419)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1420)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1421)
- Notebook #18: "Henry Wat [?] Records"
  - Kilpatrick notebook cover, "18 Henry Wat [?] Records", undated (Box 17, Folder 1422)
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 1423)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Adam Hendricks" [author?]
  - Medical formula notebook, undated (Box 17, Folder 1424)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Probably by Andy Hicks"
  - Medical formula notebook, 1890s (Box 17, Folder 1425)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Geo. Bolin Formula Book I 1890s"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1426)
  - Medical formula notebook, circa 1936 (Box 17, Folder 1427)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "dlanusi doyanisi VIII 1936"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 17, Folder 1428)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Names in English, undated (Box 17, Folder 1429)
  - Foster, James (Tsuwanosgi Atsila). Letter, 1926 July 29 (Box 17, Folder 1430)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "uwedasadi XXXIV, letters from James Foster"
  - Foster, James (Tsuwanosgi Atsila). Letter to Mr. Charlie Terrapin, 1934 February 12 (Box 17, Folder 1431)
  - Foster, James (Tsuwanosgi Atsila). Letter, 1934 May 30 (Box 17, Folder 1432)
  - Letter from American Indian Defense Association to Mr. James Foster (Tsuwanosgi Atsila)., undated (Box 17, Folder 1433)
  - Foster, Sallie (Nasi Tsuwanosgi). Letter to John Campbell, 1939 January 7 (Box 17, Folder 1434)
  - Foster, James (Tsuwanosgi Atsila). Letter, 1939 February 14 (Box 17, Folder 1435)
  - Rattler, John. Letter concerning selling of acres of Cherokee land, undated (Box 17, Folder 1436)
  - Envelope addressed to Mr. John Campbell, undated (Box 17, Folder 1437)
  - Letter or note, undated (Box 17, Folder 1438)
    Translated in Shadow, p. 88
  - Envelope addressed to Mr. John Campbell and with several letters, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 1439)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 86-88
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Uwedasat' Collection XXXVI (Letters from Dayeni Kodesgi [Dayeni Spade], sister of Ned(?) and [?] Christie)"
  - Cherokee Co. Tomatla N. C. Letter or notice, 1929 July 12 (Box 17, Folder 1440)
  - Cherokee Co. Tomatla N. C. Letter about treatment of Cherokees (east), 1931 January 4 (Box 17, Folder 1441)
  - Rattler, John. Letter, 1927 March 31 (Box 17, Folder 1442)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Uwedasadi XXXV Letters from John Rattler"
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter to Adam Hendricks, 1955 July 6 (Box 17, Folder 1443)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Adam Hendricks Collection (Letters from Watt Christie)"
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1958 March 25 (Box 17, Folder 1444)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1957 August 17 (Box 17, Folder 1445)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1958 May 11 (Box 17, Folder 1446)
  - Christie, Watt and Rita (niece). Letter, 1956 May 22 (Box 17, Folder 1447)
    Includes photograph
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1957 May 29 (Box 17, Folder 1448)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1956 March 25 (Box 17, Folder 1449)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1958 April 10 (Box 17, Folder 1450)
  - Foster, Sallie (Nasi Tsuwanosgi). Letter, 1958 June 20 (Box 17, Folder 1451)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1955 August 23 (Box 17, Folder 1452)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu). Letter, 1958 August 4 (Box 17, Folder 1453)
  - Ayatasdi George. Letter, 1945 April 2 (Box 17, Folder 1454)
  - List of names and ages, undated (Box 17, Folder 1455)
  - Unidentified fragment, damaged, undated (Box 17, Folder 1456)
  - Letter to Adawi Henili from his daughter Sallie (Salada)., 1951 January 15 (Box 17, Folder 1457)
  - Illinois Fire, Seven Clans of the Keetoowah Society, Cherokee Indians. Request to pass the Wheeler-Howard Bill with amendments., 1934 November 15 (Box 17, Folder 1458)
  - Christie, Watt (Wadi Wagigu), undated (Box 17, Folder 1459)
  - Ledger or list, undated (Box 17, Folder 1460)
  - Unidentified fragment, damaged, undated (Box 17, Folder 1461)
  - Postcard to Adam Hendricks, Mable City Okla., 1943 October (Box 17, Folder 1462)
  - Letter concerning Cherokee lands, undated (Box 17, Folder 1463)
  - Letter, 1935 November 15 (Box 17, Folder 1464)
  - Unidentified envelope fragment, damaged, undated (Box 17, Folder 1465)
  - Unidentified envelope fragment, damaged, undated (Box 17, Folder 1466)
  - Parks, J. T. Letter to Adam Hendricks, 1915 September 6 (Box 17, Folder 1467)
  - Rogers, Will. Letter to Chief Sam Smith., 1937 September 7 (Box 17, Folder 1468)
  - Tony, Lucy (Lusi Ogasdoda). Letter, 1942 May 5 (Box 17, Folder 1469)
    Translated in Shadow, pp. 93
  - Letter, 1934 August 8 (Box 17, Folder 1470)
  - Request to join the Giduwa organization, 1934 October 10 (Box 17, Folder 1471)
- Notebook #16: "Doyanisi I, II"
  - Kilpatrick notebook cover, "16 doyanisi I, II", undated (Box 18, Folder 1472)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Help Defendant in Trial" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand., 1963 August 16 (Box 18, Folder 1473)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Assist One in a Minor Crime" and "To assist One Accused of a Major Crime" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 August 23 (Box 18, Folder 1474)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, Recto: "For a Nosebleed"; Verso: "To Make a Trip Shorter", in Jack Kilpatrick's hand., 1963 August 16 (Box 18, Folder 1475)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, Recto: "For Going to Water for Protection"; Verso: "To Hunt Medicine" and "For a Sick Horse" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand., 1963 August 2 (Box 18, Folder 1476)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "For Protection While Traveling" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 August 2 (Box 18, Folder 1477)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Get a Woman" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 August 2 (Box 18, Folder 1478)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "For a Sick Horse", 1963 August 23 (Box 18, Folder 1479)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "Invocation to the Water" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand., 1963 August 23 (Box 18, Folder 1480)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Dig Up Roots" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 August 15 (Box 18, Folder 1481)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Divine With Rock or Lead" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 June 11 (Box 18, Folder 1482)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Make Rain" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, undated (Box 18, Folder 1483)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 June 16 (Box 18, Folder 1484)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "For Cutting Oneself" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 June 17 (Box 18, Folder 1485)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Cause Someone to Move" and "For a Sore or Cut" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 July (Box 18, Folder 1486)
  - Uwodigei. Medical formula, "To Fix Tobacco for Use at Night to Repel Evil Ones" and "For War" in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, 1963 June 12 (Box 18, Folder 1487)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1488)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1489)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1490)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1491)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1492)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1493)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1494)
  - Recto: Medical formula; Verso: Financial note, undated (Box 18, Folder 1495)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1496)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1497)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1498)
  - Medical formula, 1831 March (Box 18, Folder 1499)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1500)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1501)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1502)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1503)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1504)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1505)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1506)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1507)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1508)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1509)
  - Medical formula or journal, 1931 May 22 (Box 18, Folder 1510)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1511)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1512)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1513)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1514)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1515)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1516)
    Found with note in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Tsugvwa Lodi Collection (Watt Murphy) Obtained 1962 from W.J."
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1517)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1518)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1519)
    Note bottom of page in Jack Kilpatrick's hand, "Doyanisi (Waterdown)"
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1520)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1521)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1522)
  - Murphy, Watt. Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1523)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1524)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1525)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1526)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1527)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1528)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1529)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1530)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1531)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1532)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1533)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1534)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1535)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1536)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1537)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1538)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1539)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1540)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1541)
  - Medical formula, undated (Box 18, Folder 1542)